Emilia must have been talking
about the Earl John Doe Ball.
John Doe?
It implies someone of no consequence.
And his is a secret ball where
nobles hide their faces behind masks.
But why invite me to that?
Perhaps she thought it would be
the best place to gather intelligence.
The lowlifes who infest such balls
fear not even the gods.
I... see.
Now, you'll need a mask.
We'll be sneaking
into my old home, Constance.
The Castiel residence?
I was a regular at those balls.
Someone who knows something
might approach you
if you wear my old mask.
But...
Besides, this is a good opportunity
for you as well.
What do you mean?
Use your brain.
I mean to pay off your debts, of course.
All the guests will be good-for-nothings
with lurid secrets.
Find out what those are,
and take them for all they're worth.
I couldn't possibly...
No, I understand.
I didn't get it until now.
"Be you sincere."
I've always believed
that was the right thing to do.
But my father was tricked,
and Pamela framed me.
Sincerity alone won't solve anything.
I'll be wicked if that's what it takes.
So...
Take me to the Castiel residence.
A Grail casting aside
their famous sincerity? What fun.
I've yet again managed to sneak in
somewhere without issue.
But this manor is huge!
Positively enormous.
What are you doing there, girl?
Lady Scarlett?
Did you hear me?
I'm, u-um, on my way
to the dressing room.
I'm so sorry! Please excuse me!
Hey, wait.
Have you no brain in your head?
The dressing room is the other way.
Thank you very much.
My brother...
Not much resemblance, is there?
You seem quite alike to me.
Your air of superiority, the way
you feel entitled to call me "girl,"
and how you insult me
at the drop of a hat...
You're the first person
to ever say as much.
Am I really?
We do have different mothers, after all.
Constance, have you heard of
Cornelia of the Starry Crown?
Yes. The neighboring country of Faris
was once a vast empire,
and she was the last empress,
who reigned during its fall, wasn't she?
Yes, exactly.
At the time, the Faris Empire
pursued a strategy
of marrying royalty from the nations
it invaded to rule them.
Then an imperial prince
eloped with a certain lady,
and they had a daughter,
Cornelia of the Starry Crown.
Her lineage entitled her to the crowns
of vassal states as numerous as the stars,
not to mention the imperial throne.
Our own nation, Adelbide,
was part of her empire back then.
Yes, it was.
When the vassal states finally
rebelled and the empire fell,
she escaped harm
in the neutral nation of Soldita.
Time passed, and word spread
that a country girl in Soldita
carried the blood of
Cornelia of the Starry Crown.
Crownless Aliénore. She was my mother.
You mean to say you're descended
from the imperial family of Faris?
Story time is over.
My mask is in that suit of armor.
R-Right...
Your invitation?
It's in Earl John Doe's hat.
Welcome, uninvited guest.
So this...
is the Earl John Doe Ball.
What delightful tastes they have.
Never you mind.
We're going straight to see our hostess.
So it's Deborah's turn this time.
I thought as much.
You there.
What's your name?
Please, call me Eris.
My, that brings back memories.
We used to have a guest by
the same name ten years ago.
But...
she was a reckless girl.
Her head and body soon parted company.
Your head is firmly attached, I hope?
I'm amazed you can eat.
I've been so tense this whole time.
Oh, this looks tasty too!
Hmm? Something smells sweet...
Why, this takes me back. That's Jane.
Jane?
Who might she be?
Miss Eris, I believe?
That's totally Viscount Hamsworth.
U-Um...
I beg your pardon.
We hide our true selves
behind masks at this secret ball.
Please call me... Moon-Dappled Ham.
Again, you're not hiding anything!
"Hide a tree in the forest," as they say.
But what rotten wood
someone's brought tonight.
Do you not think so, my lady?
Run! The Security Force caught on!
Caught on to what?!
What's going on?!
Look at him go!
Seems I was right about those girls.
You heard what the nouveau riche hog
said about a tree in the forest.
Someone was using this whole ball
as cover for human trafficking.
N-No...
No more chitchat.
You need to run.
What are you doing? Hurry!
B-But...
Help!
No one's going to help her.
Not a soul!
Constance?!
I remember this woman from earlier.
A tattoo?
You'll get caught in the raid!
Just leave her there!
Scarlett!
Sorry. I can't do that.
Connie, you fool!
You'll be doomed if they catch you!
Even if you've done nothing wrong,
they'll put you to death
before you know it!
I'm sorry, Scarlett!
Forgive me!
If you feel the need
to apologize, get running!
You there!
What are you doing?
N-No!
What is she doing?
I should be asking you that, you lout!
Who the hell are you?!
Drawing your blade
on an unarmed young lady?
Hardly a reasonable response.
L-Lord Ulster!
But she used some kind
of strange trickery!
Should that take precedence over
saving the wounded, Jeorg Gaina?
You again, Constance Grail?
Y-Yes.
As a formality, did you have
a hand in human trafficking?
I thought not.
Then I have no cause to arrest you.
Still, three chance meetings must be fate.
Don't you think it's high time
you came clean with me?
Scarlett...
Take them for all they're worth.
Lord Ulster was born
to the House of Richelieu.
They're great nobles,
on par with the Castiels.
In which case...
W-Would you care to negotiate?!
Oh, of course. The Grails are in debt.
"If you want information, pay for it"?
He saw through me instantly!
Is that your proposal?
Er, yes.
Well, I can't say I mind.
Constance Grail, are you
willing to suffer scandal?
I've abandoned my sincerity.
I'll take whatever life throws at me.
It's a bit late to worry about that.
I see. In that case,
the simplest method...
is to get engaged.
I'd like nothing better!
Good. We'll go with that.
Getting engaged.
Wh-Wha...
What?!
S-So, you w-want to...
to pledge your engagement?
Yes. Please do the honors.
W-Well, then...
M-May the gods...
b-bless your union.
How did I get into this mess?!
Oh, honestly! Now you see why I avoid him!
Now you can clear
the Grail family's debts,
and I have a pretext
to keep an eye on you.
Naturally, you'll be free to
annul our engagement before long.
Still, are you certain?
I don't see how our engagement
benefits Your Lordship much.
To tell the truth, childish as it may be,
I don't want to marry.
But he's certainly
been married once before.
To Lady Lily Orlamunde,
who passed away two years ago.
In any case, having a fiancée
should act as a repellent.
So from my perspective,
our arrangement is purely beneficial.
Now, to business.
I see.
You want to clear Scarlett Castiel's
ghost of her false conviction.
Really, girl. Surely you should
have held something back.
Candidly, your story is preposterous.
But... it's unusually
consistent for a fiction.
And the look you get sometimes
does resemble Scarlett Castiel's.
I could almost believe you were her.
If you want to clear her name,
suit yourself.
She may be deceased, but your desire
to help others is still laudable.
Why, thank you.
What for?
Um...
That aside,
are you sure you aren't
still hiding something?
Don't.
Not a thing.
I see.
Your Lordship?
Constance Grail. Or rather, Miss Grail.
A word of warning for your future.
You are, well...
a rather poor liar.
So, what are you going to do now?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you're through
helping me, at any rate.
Huh? Why?
I mean, your debt troubles are over.
Wh-What are you laughing at?
Listen, Scarlett.
When faced with problems
I couldn't solve myself,
I was always giving them up as hopeless.
But deep inside, I was always shouting.
"Someone help me!"
And then...
Very well.
I'll help you.
Come to think of it,
I've never once told you...
Thank you for helping me.
So, now it's my turn to help you.
Right?
Stupid Connie.
That oaf Gaina can't do anything right!
What's wrong?
Remember the human trafficking ring we
rounded up at the old Montrose residence?
The slavers we caught then
took poison and died in jail.
You know how quick they are to do that!
Tying them up is basic procedure!
Kyle, did their ringleader
have a tattoo of the sun?
No, and I even checked their assholes.
Meaning they had no ties
to the Daeg Gallus organization.
Or they were simply disposable.
Well, my money's on the latter.
Guess we're back
to square one on this case.
Say, wasn't that girl at the scene again?
Constance Grail, was it?
What now? Call her in for questioning?
That won't be necessary.
What, you already questioned her?
No, we got engaged.
I'll visit the Elbaite Villa
with her tomorrow.
I expect to be back in the afternoon.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Who got engaged to whom?!
Who else but me...
and Constance Grail?
What?!
Raise your heads.
C-Certainly.
His Lordship did say that
he wanted me to meet a friend of his,
but I never dreamed
he meant the crown prince.
CROWN PRINCE ENRIQUE ADELBIDE
And from Scarlett's perspective,
this is the man who broke their betrothal.
CROWN PRINCESS CECILIA ADELBIDE
I'm so sorry I'm late!
Wow, what a surprise!
How artless! And adorable!
I'm adorable?!
That wasn't a compliment.
Wait, it wasn't?
Your name's Constance, isn't it?
May I call you Connie?
O-Of course.
And you must call me Cess.
Surely that wouldn't be proper.
Oh, but I was born
a viscount's daughter just like you.
I understand, but still...
I know!
Why don't we sit down to tea
together sometime soon?
You wouldn't mind, would you, Connie?
N-Not at all.
I know he looks scary,
and he really is scary,
but he's not a bad person.
So don't give up on him, okay?
Oh, no, I mean...
His Lordship scares me to death!
Wow. Just look at that face.
What should I do? She scares me too!
Huh?
You know, Randy, picking a day I had
official commitments wasn't very nice.
But...
Seeing you look so put out
is a rare treat, so I forgive you.
I'm to receive a distinguished guest
from the south after this.
It was an honor to see you both,
if only for the briefest of moments.
Till next time, Connie.
So cold...
That woman is as insolent as ever.
Well, overlook the slight on my account.
Changing the subject,
have you heard from Faris's emissary?
Faris, huh?
They're a proud bunch.
History is all they have to boast of.
I wouldn't be surprised if their economic
woes are as bad as rumor paints them.
When Crown Princess Cecilia
first met Crown Prince Enrique,
he must have still
been engaged to Scarlett.
I always assumed that was
the source of the tragedy. But now...
Tell me, Scarlett. What made you
dislike Princess Cecilia?
No, it was the other way around.
That woman took a dislike to me first.
What? Really?
And it wasn't as though
she disliked me in particular.
No, "dislike" isn't quite the right word.
She regarded everyone
who entered her sight with enmity.
If I had to put a name to it,
it would be...
hatred.
If that's true,
does it mean there's no true love
between the couple?
Are you lost...
young lady?
That's King Ernst.
Your Royal Majesty?!
KING ERNST ADELBIDE
You're young Miss Grail?
Y-Yes, sire!
I heard you were
the second coming of Scarlett Castiel,
but you seem a most charming young lady.
Did you know the violets in our kingdom
tend to have a reddish hue?
There's a legend about it.
A sprite that dwelt
in Adelbide's violets was careless.
It drew too close to
the dead burning in hell
and suffered horrible burns itself.
What do you make of that?
W-Well...
Step aside, Connie.
Let me think...
Perhaps the flower sprite
hoped to save the dead.
Oh? What makes you say so?
It wouldn't dare go on blooming so boldly
if it had anything to be ashamed of.
I see. You do remind me of her.
Oh? Surely you jest.
I'm certain Scarlett Castiel would say...
"The affairs of wildflowers
are no concern of mine."
Yes, that does sound like her.
I wonder what he knows about Scarlett.
RESPECTIVE ANSWERS AND BEGINNINGS